[{"answer": "You know, Piers, every day, I get up very early.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "Yet again I ask you, Ali, what the hell is going on?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Everyone has specter of Lehman Brothers hanging over them, you know?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "Well, in fact, one of the triggers today was one of Europe's largest banks, Societe Generale, losing 15 percent.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Can we see the possibility somewhere in Europe or America of banks going under of the scale of Lehman Brothers?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "When the lemmings start running towards that direction, what you want to do is run in the opposite direction.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "Is it still a sensible place to put some money right now or is it now too expensive?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "Well, double dips are actually very, very rare.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Where are we, do you think?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "I think that it's worth recognizing first that this economic challenge is more than purely a rhetorical one.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "What advise -- if you were writing speeches right now for President Obama, what advice would you give him now to ramp up the rhetoric in an effective way?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "We do.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "We need the president to reconnect with his voters really, don't we?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Well, so let me tell you exactly what happened in France.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Who cares what happens in France?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Because that enables them to have growth.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "I've said this before.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "How is he going to get Americans back to work?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Well, it's just emotional which makes it crazy, because it doesn't get you where you want to go.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "Is this sensible or is that equally crazy?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Well, the collectibles category has never kept up with real estate or stock market category.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Should people look to diversify into, you know, certainly more random investments?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Well, I agree.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Because if you can't trust your bank, who can you trust?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "In a sense, that's true.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Finally, Dave -- briefly if you don't mind -- is it ostrich time, in the sense that when these big things start exploding in this volatile way, is sometimes the best thing to do to stick your head straight in the sand and keep it there until it all blows over?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Well, I'm certainly proud to be an American.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "Or is that pride getting dented?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Not her particularly.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "Do you find yourself nodding when you hear her speak?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Yes, sure.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "Do you think the reputation of America is getting damaged badly in all this?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "I don't know they're the enemy.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "Do you think that's right?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "I'm taking the hit.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "Do you think more American business people should be doing that, should be looking more internally now?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "I don't know that it's the American way, but it's my way.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "To actually take a hit in the way you're describing is not really the American way, is it?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Paying their bills and keeping their job.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "What's the number one concern for them?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Yeah, I think so.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "If you're the president, is that where you want to see the focus now, getting Americans back to work?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "No, I didn't thankfully.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Did you have to do that all year?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "ORGAN: He is.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Isn't he though?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Well, my first divorce is not on there.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Of all of those things, what was the worst, would you say?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "DKINS: It's easier to deal with somebody trying to kill you than somebody saying they don't love you anymore.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "You mean your first divorce was worse than the second wife shooting you in the chest, was it?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "Yeah, I do remember thinking that.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Did you think you were going to die?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Your wife, who I had the pleasure of meeting a few times on \"Apprentice\" -- delightful lady.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Yeah, I've had some things happen to me that I didn't feel like I really deserve, you know?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "She remembers you hitting on her when she was up at -- and that's cool.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Is she well?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Yeah, it's part of the gig.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "Is that -- is that the nature of the beast?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "Do you still feel that?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "You kind of got it all out of your system?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "You know, I would like to be able to say yes, but I've moved now 17, 18 years past that.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "Does he still act as kind of a quiet motivating factor to you in your career, in your life?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "Oh, he'd be so proud.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "What would he have made of what's happened to you, do you think?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "I think what you should do before the markets open is pick up some Pepto-Bismol on your way in.", "docId": "110810pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Ali, I barely know how to ask you this, but have you got any idea what's going to happen in the markets tomorrow?", "qSentId": 593}]